Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪My heart shattered, withered into pieces♪
♪تحطم قلبي، ذبل إلى قطع♪
♪Yet I still can't find a trace of you♪
♪ولكنني لا أزال غير قادر على العثور على أي أثر لك♪
♪Like a whale drowning in the cracks of the deep sea♪
♪مثل حوت يغرق في شقوق البحر العميق♪
♪Thinking of you, I lose myself completely♪
♪أفكر فيك، وأفقد نفسي تمامًا♪
♪My heart shattered, withered into pieces♪
♪تحطم قلبي، ذبل إلى قطع♪
♪Humbly, I still long to search for you♪
♪بكل تواضع، ما زلت أتوق للبحث عنك♪
♪Screaming as I fall into the darkest abyss♪
♪أصرخ وأنا أسقط في الهاوية المظلمة♪
♪Echoing back is only the tide of loneliness♪
♪العودة إلى الوراء ليست سوى موجة الوحدة♪
♪Overestimating myself♪
♪المبالغة في تقدير نفسي♪
=Marry Him in Her Place=
=تزوجيه مكانها=
=Episode 16=
=الحلقة 16=
Go ahead.
تفضل.
Mr. Li, how have you been lately?
السيد لي، كيف حالك في الآونة الأخيرة؟
Quite well.
جيد جداً.
Thank you for asking.
شكرا لسؤالك.
Madam Lin.
Madam Lin.
Chief Song.
رئيس الأغنية.
Why didn't Madam Lin greet the hosts
لماذا لم تستقبل السيدة لين المضيفين؟
of today's banquet?
من مأدبة اليوم؟
Afraid of me?
خائفة مني؟
Chief Song, you hold my secret in your hands.
يا رئيس سونغ، أنت تحمل سري بين يديك.
Of course, I'm afraid.
بالطبع، أنا خائف.
Madam Lin.
Madam Lin.
Listen to my advice.
استمع إلى نصيحتي.
Before you act or make decisions,
قبل أن تتصرف أو تتخذ قرارًا،
it's best to leave yourself a way out.
من الأفضل أن تترك لنفسك مخرجًا.
Otherwise, if your backers fall,
وإلا، إذا سقط داعموك،
you might lose your life.
ربما تخسر حياتك.
Thanks for your concern, Chief Song,
شكرا لاهتمامك، رئيس سونغ،
but you better save this advice for yourself.
ولكن من الأفضل أن تحتفظ بهذه النصيحة لنفسك.
There are many guests today.
هناك العديد من الضيوف اليوم.
If anything embarrassing happens,
إذا حدث أي شيء محرج،
I wonder if Chief Song will still remain as calm as now.
أتساءل عما إذا كان الرئيس سونغ سيظل هادئًا كما هو الآن.
Chief Song, ignoring your own wife
رئيس سونغ، تجاهل زوجتك
and all these merchants,
وكل هؤلاء التجار،
chatting so happily with my wife here,
أتحدث بسعادة مع زوجتي هنا،
shows you really haven't taken Mayor Song's words to heart.
يُظهر أنك لم تأخذ كلمات رئيس البلدية سونغ على محمل الجد.
We've known each other for years.
لقد عرفنا بعضنا البعض لسنوات.
Your overprotective behavior for your wife
سلوكك المفرط في حماية زوجتك
really opens my eyes.
يفتح عيني حقا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Then I wish you both a wonderful time today.
ثم أتمنى لكما وقتًا رائعًا اليوم.
Guang, go.
قوانغ، اذهب.
Mother.
الأم.
Madam Song already has children.
السيدة سونغ لديها أطفال بالفعل.
This wealthy family is such a mess.
هذه العائلة الغنية هي فوضى عارمة.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Take him away.
خذه بعيدا.
Wait.
انتظر.
Chief Song.
رئيس الأغنية.
Mr. Lu and his son were brought by me.
لقد أحضرت السيد لو وابنه.
What do you mean by this?
ماذا تقصد بهذا؟
So it was Mr. Lin who brought them.
وكان السيد لين هو الذي أحضرهم.
I thought they were bothering my wife.
اعتقدت أنهم يضايقون زوجتي.
I thought they were here to cause trouble.
اعتقدت أنهم هنا لإحداث المشاكل.
What a coincidence.
يا لها من مصادفة!
Mr. Lu asked me to find someone for him.
لقد طلب مني السيد لو أن أجد له شخصًا.
Looks like I found them.
يبدو أنني وجدتهم.
Mr. Lin, found them.
السيد لين، وجدهم.
She's the one I was looking for.
إنها الشخص الذي كنت أبحث عنه.
You're lying. I don't even know you.
أنت تكذب. أنا لا أعرفك حتى.
What a scoundrel.
يا له من وغد!
Father.
أب.
You, Lu Man.
أنت، لو مان.
You lied to me about making money in the city.
لقد كذبت علي بشأن كسب المال في المدينة.
Turns out you were climbing the social ladder.
اتضح أنك كنت تتسلق السلم الاجتماعي.
Our child is already this big.
طفلنا أصبح كبيرًا بالفعل.
You, a married woman,
أنتِ امرأة متزوجة،
actually did something so shameless.
لقد فعلت شيئا وقحا للغاية.
If my mother hadn't taken in a lonely and helpless you back then,
لو لم تأخذك أمي وحيدًا وعاجزًا في ذلك الوقت،
you wouldn't have the life you have now.
لن تحصل على الحياة التي تعيشها الآن.
Everyone,
الجميع،
help me judge this.
ساعدني على الحكم على هذا.
Is there anyone who bullies their husband like this?
هل هناك من يتنمر على زوجها بهذه الطريقة؟
Guang.
قوانغ.
Take a good look.
خذ نظرة جيدة.
Your mother doesn't want us anymore.
والدتك لم تعد تريدنا بعد الآن.
Mother.
الأم.
Guang, don't listen to him.
قوانغ، لا تستمع إليه.
I don't mean that.
انا لا اقصد ذلك
How could Miss Liang have such a big child?
كيف يمكن للسيدة ليانغ أن يكون لها طفل كبير مثل هذا؟
There's something fishy here.
هناك شيء مريب هنا.
Isn't she Miss Liang?
أليست هي الآنسة ليانغ؟
Why is she called Lu Man?
لماذا يطلق عليها اسم لو مان؟
Could it be that she cheated on Chief Song?
هل يمكن أن تكون قد خانت رئيس سونغ؟
(Now let's see how you explain this.)
(الآن دعونا نرى كيف تشرح هذا.)
Zhichu.
تشيتشو.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Come in.
ادخل.
(Uncle Er.)
(العم إير.)
Mayor Song.
أغنية رئيسية.
There's something
هناك شيئا ما
Liang family has hidden this from you too long.
لقد أخفت عائلة ليانغ هذا الأمر عنك لفترة طويلة.
It's been weighing on my conscience.
لقد كان الأمر يثقل كاهلي.
Today I must reveal it
اليوم يجب أن أكشفه
to the public.
إلى الجمهور.
Liang Yi went missing for two years at sixteen.
اختفى ليانغ يي لمدة عامين عندما كان في السادسة عشر من عمره.
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
my eldest brother took Liang Yi out of town for business,
لقد أخذ أخي الأكبر ليانغ يي خارج المدينة للعمل،
but unexpectedly, she got lost.
ولكن بشكل غير متوقع، فقدت.
Back then my eldest brother was frantic.
في ذلك الوقت كان أخي الأكبر في حالة من الذعر.
He searched everywhere.
لقد بحث في كل مكان.
He searched for over a year.
لقد بحث لمدة تزيد عن عام.
He finally found her.
لقد وجدها أخيرا.
But unexpectedly, it was already too late.
ولكن بشكل غير متوقع، كان الوقت قد فات بالفعل.
The Lu family had bought her and taken her.
لقد اشترتها عائلة لو وأخذتها.
She even had a child.
حتى أنها كان لديها طفل.
My eldest brother was heartbroken,
لقد كان أخي الأكبر حزينًا للغاية،
in deep anguish.
في ألم عميق.
But family disgrace shouldn't be made public.
لكن لا ينبغي أن يتم الإعلان عن العار العائلي .
So he hid this part of her past.
فأخفى ​​هذا الجزء من ماضيها.
Besides, my brother truly
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، أخي حقا
cherished the marriage arranged between Liang Yi and Zhichu.
اعتز بالزواج الذي تم بين ليانغ يي وزيتشيو.
He was confused at the time
لقد كان مرتبكًا في ذلك الوقت
and concealed the truth.
وأخفى الحقيقة.
In the end, he still decided to marry Liang Yi into the Song family.
وفي النهاية، قرر الزواج من ليانغ يي في عائلة سونغ.
Mayor Song,
عمدة سونغ،
please be magnanimous.
من فضلك كن كريما.
Considering my brother has passed away,
بما أن أخي قد توفي،
I beg your forgiveness.
أطلب منك السماح.
If there's any blame, put it on me.
إذا كان هناك أي لوم، ضعه علي.
I'll take it all.
سوف آخذها كلها
Mayor Song,
عمدة سونغ،
Liang family has wronged you.
لقد ظلمتك عائلة ليانغ.
We have wronged you.
لقد ظلمناك
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I won't allow them to slander me like this.
لن اسمح لهم بأن يشوهوا سمعتي بهذه الطريقة.
Turning truth into lies.
تحويل الحقيقة إلى أكاذيب.
In what identity are you stepping out?
في أي هوية أنت تخرج؟
Xu Yin?
شو يين؟
Or Liang Yi?
أو ليانغ يي؟
I sincerely apologize
أنا أعتذر بصدق
for making everyone witness this.
لجعل الجميع يشهدون هذا.
Regarding today's incident,
بخصوص حادثة اليوم،
I hope everyone can understand the hardship behind it.
آمل أن يتمكن الجميع من فهم الصعوبات التي يواجهونها.
Do not speak carelessly.
لا تتكلم بلا مبالاة.
Take all of them back.
خذهم جميعا مرة أخرى.
This matter is extremely serious.
هذه المسألة خطيرة للغاية.
I will interrogate it personally.
سأستجوبه شخصيا.
Mayor Song.
أغنية رئيسية.
Mr. Lu and Guang were brought by me.
لقد أحضرت السيد لو و قوانغ.
Besides, they are also victims.
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، فإنهم ضحايا أيضًا.
Please allow them to leave.
من فضلك اسمح لهم بالمغادرة.
How about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
If you need the father and son to testify,
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى شهادة الأب والابن،
just tell me.
فقط أخبرني.
I will personally bring them to your residence.
سأحضرهم شخصيًا إلى مقر إقامتك.
Then I'll trouble you.
ثم سأزعجك.
(So the one who really betrayed my father was Uncle Er.)
(لذا فإن الشخص الذي خان والدي حقًا كان العم إير.)
You thought capturing the Lu father and son would give me leverage.
لقد اعتقدت أن القبض على الأب والابن لو سوف يمنحني نفوذًا.
Trying to fight me?
تحاول قتالي؟
Too naive.
ساذج جداً.
Xiazhu. I missed you so much. Give me a kiss.
شيازهو، اشتقت إليكِ كثيرًا. قبّليني.
No.
لا.
So pretentious.
متكلف للغاية.
Come on, give me a kiss.
تعال أعطني قبلة.
Pretentious.
متكلف.
Xiaojiao.
شياو جياو.
Don't leave.
لا تغادر.
Wait a moment.
انتظر لحظة.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Is everything ready?
هل كل شيء جاهز؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Good.
جيد.
Second Master has great tolerance for alcohol.
يتمتع المعلم الثاني بقدرة كبيرة على تحمل الكحول.
Good wine.
نبيذ جيد.
Qiushuang, you smell wonderful.
كيوشوانغ، رائحتك رائعة.
Come.
يأتي.
Let me kiss you.
دعني أقبلك.
Second Master,
المعلم الثاني
let me toast you again.
دعني أحتفل بك مرة أخرى.
Your skin is so fair.
بشرتك عادلة جداً.
So smooth.
سلسة جداً.
Qiushuang.
كيوشوانغ.
I will be gentle later.
سأكون لطيفًا لاحقًا.
You really can drink.
يمكنك الشرب حقا.
Good wine.
نبيذ جيد.
Fill it up.
املأها.
Second Master.
المعلم الثاني.
Is this drug reliable?
هل هذا الدواء موثوق؟
Don't worry, Madam Lin.
لا تقلقي سيدتي لين.
When he wakes up, he'll feel weak and drenched in cold sweat.
عندما يستيقظ، سوف يشعر بالضعف والعرق البارد.
Just like being possessed by something evil.
تمامًا كما لو كنت مسكونًا بشيء شرير.
I've cleared the area.
لقد قمت بتطهير المنطقة.
Ask anything you need.
اسأل عن أي شيء تحتاجه.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Someone come!
تعالوا أحد!
Is anyone there?
هل هناك أحد؟
Qiushuang!
كيوشوانغ!
Someone come!
تعالوا أحد!
Amitabha.
أميتابها.
Buddha, please protect me.
بوذا، من فضلك احميني.
Return my life to me!
رجع لي حياتي!
I died so miserably!
لقد مت بائسًا جدًا!
Uncle Er.
العم إير.
You...
أنت...
Liang Yi?
ليانغ يي؟
Uncle Er.
العم إير.
Where is my father?
أين والدي؟
Why can't I find him?
لماذا لا أستطيع العثور عليه؟
Your father... Hasn't he already passed away?
والدك... ألم يمت بالفعل؟
Impossible.
مستحيل.
How could my father be dead?
كيف يمكن أن يكون والدي ميتا؟
It's true. I'm not lying.
إنه صحيح. أنا لا أكذب.
Your father had already died on your wedding day.
لقد توفي والدك في يوم زفافك.
Every injustice has a culprit.
لكل ظلم مذنب.
If you have matters, don't come to me. Don't come to me.
إذا كان لديك أمور فلا تأت إليّ. لا تأت إليّ.
Go to Song Zhichu.
اذهب إلى أغنية Zhichu.
Why did Song Zhichu kill my father?
لماذا قتل سونغ تشيتشو والدي؟
Because...
لأن...
Say it.
قلها.
Because your father discovered that Song Zhichu
لأن والدك اكتشف أن سونغ تشيتشو
and I were secretly using the Liang family
وكنت أستخدم عائلة ليانغ سراً
to transport opium.
لنقل الأفيون.
He wanted to report us to Song Ming.
أراد أن يبلغ عنا إلى سونغ مينغ.
I acted to protect myself,
لقد تصرفت لحماية نفسي،
and quickly informed Song Zhichu.
وأبلغ سونغ تشيتشو بسرعة.
Who knew Song Zhichu would be so ruthless?
من كان ليتصور أن سونغ تشيتشو سيكون بهذه القسوة؟
He's too cruel.
إنه قاسي للغاية.
He even killed his father-in-law.
حتى أنه قتل والد زوجته.
So you also perjured yourself for him against your conscience.
فأنت أيضاً كذبت على نفسك من أجله ضد ضميرك.
Calling black white.
نداء الأسود أبيض.
I had no choice.
لم يكن لدي خيار.
You know,
أنت تعرف،
Song Zhichu
أغنية تشيتشو
is madman.
هو مجنون.
He is ruthless.
إنه لا يرحم.
Did Song Ming know about you and Song Zhichu transporting opium?
هل كان سونغ مينغ على علم بقيامك أنت وسونغ تشيتشو بنقل الأفيون؟
There's no way he could know.
ليس هناك طريقة لمعرفة ذلك.
He is the mayor.
هو رئيس البلدية.
Moreover, the anti-opium campaign in Rong City
علاوة على ذلك، فإن حملة مكافحة الأفيون في مدينة رونغ
was your father and Song Ming's joint effort.
كان هذا نتيجة جهد مشترك بين والدك وسونغ مينغ.
I've said all I can.
لقد قلت كل ما بوسعي.
Go back to where you came from.
ارجع إلى حيث أتيت منه.
I will make sure to send you more money so that your life there is well-provided.
سأتأكد من إرسال المزيد من المال لك حتى تكون حياتك هناك جيدة.
Alright?
على ما يرام؟
I already old. I can't take much fright.
لقد كبرت بالفعل، لا أستطيع تحمل الكثير من الخوف.
Sign this confession.
توقيع هذا الاعتراف.
No.
لا.
Song Zhichu...
سونغ تشيتشو...
He will kill me.
سوف يقتلني.
I'll be dead.
سوف اموت
If you don't sign,
إذا لم توقع،
I'll take you to the underworld to see my father
سآخذك إلى العالم السفلي لرؤية والدي
and make you suffer in hell for eternity.
ويجعلك تعاني في الجحيم إلى الأبد.
You won't die a good death.
لن تموت موتة جيدة.
I'll sign.
سأوقع.
(The sinner)
(الخاطئ)
Uncle Er,
العم إير،
I will haunt you forever.
سأطاردك إلى الأبد.
You'll never be rid of me in your life.
لن تتخلص مني أبدًا في حياتك.
I want you to pay with your life.
أريدك أن تدفع بحياتك.
No!
لا!
There...
هناك...
There's a ghost!
هناك شبح!
Making him confess is simple.
جعله يعترف أمر بسيط.
Why torture yourself like this?
لماذا تعذب نفسك هكذا؟
Why can brothers use each other
لماذا يستطيع الأخوة أن يستغلوا بعضهم البعض؟
and scheme against each other?
والتخطيط ضد بعضهم البعض؟
When my father was alive, he treated Uncle Er well.
عندما كان والدي على قيد الحياة، كان يعامل عمي إير بشكل جيد.
And yet he could betray like this.
ورغم هذا فإنه يستطيع أن يخون بهذه الطريقة.
(I really didn't expect Miss Liang to be alive.)
(لم أتوقع حقًا أن تكون الآنسة ليانغ على قيد الحياة.)
(If I tell Chief Song about this...)
(إذا أخبرت الرئيس سونغ بهذا الأمر...)
Is there really no karma in this world?
هل حقا لا يوجد كارما في هذا العالم؟
If not,
إذا لم يكن كذلك،
I will fight for justice on your behalf.
سأقاتل من أجل العدالة نيابة عنك.
♪Awakened by the rain on the silent sea♪
♪استيقظت على صوت المطر في البحر الصامت♪
♪I hear my heartbeat roaring in sorrow♪
♪أسمع دقات قلبي تزمجر في حزن♪
♪I was abandoned♪
♪لقد تم التخلي عني♪
♪Dreaming of you in the same place♪
♪أحلم بك في نفس المكان♪
♪Cold eyes♪
♪عيون باردة♪
♪My heart shattered, withered into pieces♪
♪تحطم قلبي، ذبل إلى قطع♪
♪Raise the big screen, start your pretentious performance♪
♪ارفع الشاشة الكبيرة، وابدأ أدائك المتكلف♪
♪The most foolish gambler♪
♪المقامر الأكثر حماقة♪
♪Would treat love as prey, caring nothing♪
♪أعامل الحب كفريسة، لا أهتم بأي شيء♪
♪You pretend to be innocent, yet the red wounds are vivid in my mind♪
♪تتظاهر بالبراءة، لكن الجروح الحمراء واضحة في ذهني♪
♪Such a hypocritical gift♪
♪هذه هدية منافقة♪
♪Victory is revealed too quickly♪
♪النصر يتكشف بسرعة كبيرة♪
♪I treated you as my salvation♪
♪لقد عاملتك كخلاصي♪
♪You treated me as a toy♪
♪لقد عاملتني كلعبة♪
♪And we both fall into endless loneliness♪
♪وكلا منا سقط في الوحدة التي لا نهاية لها♪
♪I loved too deeply♪
♪لقد أحببت بعمق شديد♪
♪Your methods are too cruel♪
♪طرقك قاسية جدًا♪
♪Once devotion is desecrated, only waiting for your disgrace♪
♪بمجرد تدنيس الإخلاص، لن تنتظر سوى عارك♪
♪I treated you as my salvation♪
♪لقد عاملتك كخلاصي♪
♪You treated me as a toy♪
♪لقد عاملتني كلعبة♪
♪And we both fall into endless loneliness♪♪
♪وكلا منا سقط في الوحدة التي لا نهاية لها♪♪
♪I loved too deeply♪
♪لقد أحببت بعمق شديد♪
♪Your methods are too cruel♪
♪طرقك قاسية جدًا♪
♪Once devotion is desecrated, only waiting for your disgrace♪
♪بمجرد تدنيس الإخلاص، لن تنتظر سوى عارك♪
♪Curtain call♪
♪استدعاء الستار♪